[
    {
        "id": "01",
        "question" : "What is the capital city of Myanmar",
        "options": [
            "Mandalay",
            "Naypyidaw",
            "Yangon",
            "Bagan"
        ],
        "answer": "Naypyidaw"
    },
    {
        "id": "02",
        "question" : "Which river is the longest in Myanmar?",
        "options": [
            "Irrawaddy River",
            "Chindwin River",
            "Salween River",
            "Sittaung River"    
        ],
        "answer": "Irrawaddy River"
    },
    {
        "id": "03",
        "question" : "In which year did Myanmar gain independence from Birtish rule?",
        "options": [
            "1945",
            "1947",
            "1948",
            "1950"
        ],
        "answer": "1948"
    },
    {
        "id": "04",
        "question" : "Who was the leader of Myanmar's independence movement and the country's first Prime Minister",
        "options": [
            "U Nu",
            "Aung San",
            "Ne Win",
            "U Thant"
        ],
        "answer": "Aung San"
    },
    {
        "id": "05",
        "question" : "What is the traditional Burmese dress for men called?",
        "options": [
            "Longyi",
            "Htaingmathein",
            "Pasoe",
            "None of the above."
        ],
        "answer": "Pasoe"
    },
    {
        "id": "06",
        "question" : "What was the Myanmar's former name before it was officially changed in 1989?",
        "options": [
            "Siam",
            "Rangoon",
            "Ceylon",
            "Burma"
        ],
        "answer": "Burma"
    },
    {
        "id": "07",
        "question" : "Who is the Nobel Peace Prize lauerate known for her efforts in promoting demmocracy in Myanmar",
        "options": [
            "Aung San Suu Kyi",
            "Thein Sein",
            "Min Aung Hlaing",
            "Than Shwe"
        ],
        "answer": "Aung San Suu Kyi"
    },
    {
        "id": "08",
        "question" : "Which natural resource is a significant export of Myanmar?",
        "options": [
            "Gold",
            "Natural gas",
            "Humans",
            "Teas"
        ],
        "answer": "Natural gas"
    },
    {
        "id": "09",
        "question" : "Which ancient city in Myanmar is famous for its thousands of Buddhist temples and pagodas?",
        "options": [
            "Mrauk U",
            "Mandalay",
            "Pyay",
            "Bagan"
        ],
        "answer": "Bagan"
    },
    {
        "id": "10",
        "question" : "Which traditional festival in Myanmar involves water fights and is celebrated in April?",
        "options": [
            "Tazaungdaing",
            "Thadingyut",
            "Thingyan",
            "Kason"
        ],
        "answer": "Thingyan"
    }
]